{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987707520","data":{"timestamp":" 946987707520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987713975","data":{"timestamp":" 946987713975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987744400","data":{"timestamp":" 946987744400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987781465","data":{"timestamp":" 946987781465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987813967","data":{"timestamp":" 946987813967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987825329","data":{"timestamp":" 946987825329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987837237","data":{"timestamp":" 946987837237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987896599","data":{"timestamp":" 946987896598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987917906","data":{"timestamp":" 946987917905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987933713","data":{"timestamp":" 946987933713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987942745","data":{"timestamp":" 946987942744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987946618","data":{"timestamp":" 946987946618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987979649","data":{"timestamp":" 946987979648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987983948","data":{"timestamp":" 946987983947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946987987677","data":{"timestamp":" 946987987676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988056493","data":{"timestamp":" 946988056493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988059746","data":{"timestamp":" 946988059746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988063491","data":{"timestamp":" 946988063491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988067435","data":{"timestamp":" 946988067435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988070729","data":{"timestamp":" 946988070729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988074653","data":{"timestamp":" 946988074653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988087280","data":{"timestamp":" 946988087280"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988094261","data":{"timestamp":" 946988094261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988100647","data":{"timestamp":" 946988100647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988106405","data":{"timestamp":" 946988106405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 54afd40d-c5a8-4092-98b0-79d4e0930f31"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988128928","data":{"timestamp":" 946988128927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988131075","data":{"timestamp":" 946988131074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988133226","data":{"timestamp":" 946988133224"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988136454","data":{"timestamp":" 946988136454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988138735","data":{"timestamp":" 946988138734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988140974","data":{"timestamp":" 946988140973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988143879","data":{"timestamp":" 946988143878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988146095","data":{"timestamp":" 946988146095"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988148272","data":{"timestamp":" 946988148272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988151494","data":{"timestamp":" 946988151493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988153620","data":{"timestamp":" 946988153619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988155715","data":{"timestamp":" 946988155715"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988158710","data":{"timestamp":" 946988158709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988160955","data":{"timestamp":" 946988160954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988163201","data":{"timestamp":" 946988163201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988166183","data":{"timestamp":" 946988166183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988168523","data":{"timestamp":" 946988168522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988170883","data":{"timestamp":" 946988170883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988173958","data":{"timestamp":" 946988173957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988176118","data":{"timestamp":" 946988176117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988178258","data":{"timestamp":" 946988178257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988181411","data":{"timestamp":" 946988181410"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988183645","data":{"timestamp":" 946988183644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988185847","data":{"timestamp":" 946988185846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988189028","data":{"timestamp":" 946988189027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988191459","data":{"timestamp":" 946988191458"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988193872","data":{"timestamp":" 946988193871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988197054","data":{"timestamp":" 946988197053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988199304","data":{"timestamp":" 946988199303"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988201548","data":{"timestamp":" 946988201548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988204515","data":{"timestamp":" 946988204514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988206745","data":{"timestamp":" 946988206744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988208976","data":{"timestamp":" 946988208975"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988211887","data":{"timestamp":" 946988211887"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988214236","data":{"timestamp":" 946988214236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988216584","data":{"timestamp":" 946988216583"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988219755","data":{"timestamp":" 946988219755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988222137","data":{"timestamp":" 946988222136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988224538","data":{"timestamp":" 946988224537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988227539","data":{"timestamp":" 946988227539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988229852","data":{"timestamp":" 946988229851"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988232134","data":{"timestamp":" 946988232133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988235411","data":{"timestamp":" 946988235411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988237673","data":{"timestamp":" 946988237672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988239910","data":{"timestamp":" 946988239909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988243303","data":{"timestamp":" 946988243302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988245756","data":{"timestamp":" 946988245755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988248190","data":{"timestamp":" 946988248189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988251101","data":{"timestamp":" 946988251101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988253358","data":{"timestamp":" 946988253357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988255540","data":{"timestamp":" 946988255539"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988258923","data":{"timestamp":" 946988258923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988261271","data":{"timestamp":" 946988261271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988263615","data":{"timestamp":" 946988263615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988266773","data":{"timestamp":" 946988266772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988269006","data":{"timestamp":" 946988269005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988271234","data":{"timestamp":" 946988271234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988274172","data":{"timestamp":" 946988274172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988276249","data":{"timestamp":" 946988276249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988278322","data":{"timestamp":" 946988278322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988281430","data":{"timestamp":" 946988281429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988283649","data":{"timestamp":" 946988283649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988285851","data":{"timestamp":" 946988285850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988289049","data":{"timestamp":" 946988289049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988291223","data":{"timestamp":" 946988291222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988293425","data":{"timestamp":" 946988293425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988296610","data":{"timestamp":" 946988296609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988298942","data":{"timestamp":" 946988298942"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988301289","data":{"timestamp":" 946988301288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988304446","data":{"timestamp":" 946988304445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988306772","data":{"timestamp":" 946988306771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988309077","data":{"timestamp":" 946988309076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988312482","data":{"timestamp":" 946988312481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988312615","data":{"timestamp":" 946988312614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" 359b7aaf-adda-487c-83b0-2148609f11a4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988357382","data":{"timestamp":" 946988357382"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" c66067d0-2578-4a2f-a5ed-dba27a080b66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988396724","data":{"timestamp":" 946988396724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" c66067d0-2578-4a2f-a5ed-dba27a080b66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946988396849","data":{"timestamp":" 946988396849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_150737"," gameId":" c66067d0-2578-4a2f-a5ed-dba27a080b66"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}